<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Minirah&#39;s blog</title>
    <link>https://minirah.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Minirah&#39;s blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2022 21:30:04 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://minirah.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Things I Wish to Learn</title>
      <link>https://minirah.github.io/posts/things-i-wish-to-learn/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 08:11:30 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://minirah.github.io/posts/things-i-wish-to-learn/</guid>
      <description>If only there is a way to know everything without effort!!!
I wish to learn all these stuff either for the fun of it or because I consider these will somehow magically transform me into a better or intelligent person(which I know is not true). But what is life if not trying out stuff you wanna do with the limited time you have been given.
I&amp;rsquo;ll update this list
Learn another language (probably Hindi) apart from my mother tongue &amp;amp; English At least good enough to watch movie without subtitles and have a conversation with a stranger Learn to swim At least good enough to float in a place for long time Learn math concepts Will this make me a better person?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://minirah.github.io/about-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 06:22:31 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://minirah.github.io/about-me/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m a guy from a country with more than a billion people. Not that hard to figure out which. I like people.
Enjoys in no particular order - movies, reading, company of my people, working out, hikes, short trips, long trips, vibing to music, singing along my favorite songs, arguing, play fighting, memes, dancing like skydancer, food. A lot more stuff is not mentioned.
Based on employer, I am either a software developer or software engineer or software development engineer or project engineer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Why blog?</title>
      <link>https://minirah.github.io/posts/why-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 19:25:27 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://minirah.github.io/posts/why-blog/</guid>
      <description> To jot down thoughts - otherwise and useful I like writing. But the thought of writing to a personal notes folder which even I won&amp;rsquo;t ever likely read again feels odd &amp;amp; dis-heartening. This way at least the all gobbling google crawler will read what I scribble My random corner in the internet to ramble into the ether Just because I can </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
